>> Jem Young: 现在我想 SSH 到我的服务器。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
now I want to SSH into my server.
现在，我将创建与服务器的安全连接。
Now that I'm going to create
a secure connection to my server.
缺省情况下，用户为 root用户。
The user that is,
by default is root, the root user.
所以我现在就去试试
So I'm going to try that now.
因此， SSH 根位于我的 IP 地址。
So SSH root at my IP address.
> > Jem Young: 我要打 " 是"
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And I'm gonna hit Yes.
我只是说我从没见过这台服务器
It's just saying hey,
I've never met this server before.
确定这是要连接到的内容吗 ?
Are you sure this is what
you wanna connect to?
这很有用因为说有人侵入了你的服务器
Which is really useful because let's
say someone hacked your server and
把它拿走
took it over.
签名会有一点不同
The signature is gonna be
a little bit different.
我很想知道，我正尝试在这个服务器上使用 SSH ，但是
And it's really useful to know like hey,
I'm trying to SSH into this server but
它已经不工作了
it's not working anymore.
如果你得到的是 SSHing的话
And if you ever get something
like you're SSHing,
您已连接到服务器，并且 SHA 签名已更改，
you're connected to a server and
the SHA signature is changed,
你应该小心一点因为有些东西有点太 awry了
you should be a little careful
because something's a little bit awry.
通常没什么可只是个头头
Usually it's nothing but
it's just a heads up.
我只是想说 " 是"
I'm just gonna say yes.
拒绝了伙计那里发生了什么
Denied, man what happened there?
那么，缺省密钥对是标识为 SSH 的标识。
Well, what happened is the default
key pair is ID underscore SSH.
然后， SSH 将首先尝试查找。
And SSH is going to try
to look there first.
如果这不起作用的话我就不知道了
If that doesn't work,
it's going to be like, I don't know,
您的密钥与我们在服务器中的公用密钥不匹配。
your key is not matching into the public
key that we have in the server.
所以我们要做的是 SSH 破折号
So what we need to do is SSH dash I, and
我们会把我们通过的那个私人钥匙的名字通过
we're going to pass in the name of
that private key that we passed in.
那么 fsfe2 ，然后我们输入根@
So, fsfe2 and then we type root@
>> Jem Young: 我在我的服务器上
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And I am on my server,
你就在你的服务器上
you're on your server.
如果你想看看发生了什么
And if you wanna see what's happening, and
我今次不会通过破折号，我只是说根 @ IP 地址。
I won't pass the dash I this time around,
I'm just gonna say root @ IP address.
我要说 " V " 它会给我更多细节
I'm gonna say dash V and
it's gonna give me more details.
如果你想知道，为什么这件事不被接受呢 ?
This is helpful if you try to figure out
hey, why is this thing not being accepted?
为什么这一次的工作，无论如何都不应该起作用。
Why did that work this time,
that should not have worked, anyways.
这比你想知道的细节更详细
And this just more detail than
you want to know but it's used to
如果您感到困惑，那么仪表板命令可用于调试。
the dashboard command is useful for
debugging if you're ever confused.
然后退出我的服务器，我就可以在我的正常计算机上输入一个出口。
And exit my server, I can just type
exit in a back to my normal computer.
你知道那是个痛苦
You know that was, that was a pain.
我不希望每次都这样
I don't want to type
that every single time.
我们要做的就是把它加到钥匙链上
So what we're gonna do is we're
gonna add it to the key chain.
这个关于 OSX 的伟大之处在于它有一个密钥链的概念。
This a great thing about OSX is
it has this concept of keychain.
大多数计算机都这样做，我不确定 Windows 是否会这样做，但我们会添加这个
Most computers do, I'm not sure if
Windows does, but we're gonna add this
锁链所以它是它检查的普通钥匙的一部分
to the keychain so that it's part
of the regular keys that it checks.
所以当你进入服务器的时候，它会说，这个是它。
So when you SSH into a server,
it's gonna say, this one is it.
这个是这个，不是吗 ?
This one is this one, no, yes?
>> 演讲者 2: 我想说，如果你成功了，你就不用这么做了
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I was gonna say, you don't
have to do that once you've successfully
它会自动将它添加到您的密钥链中。
connected, it automatically
adds it to your keychain.
>> Jem Young: 真的吗 ? >演讲者 2: 这就是为什么它没有问你
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Really?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That's why it didn't ask you
第二次了
the second time.
>> Jem Young: 所以我这样说是因为我在另一台计算机上尝试了这个
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So I will say this because
I tried this on a different computer, not
每个密钥链自动配置为每次将密钥添加到代理程序。
every keychain is automatically configured
to add the keys to the agent every time.
有些电脑是
Some computers are.
但这一点非常好。
But that's a really good point.
我觉得这个版本的 OSX 的现代版本就是这样
I think the modern version of whatever
version of OSX I'm in does that, but
如果没有，您可以说 VI ，我们将修改 SSH 配置。
just in case it doesn't, you can say VI
and we're going to modify the SSH config.
所以我将会说清楚的 vi ) 点 SSH 的配置。
So I'm going to say clear vi
tilde dot SSH slash config.
>> Jem Young: And KeysTo the agent 仅表示，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
the AddKeysTo the agent just means,
每次成功连接到服务器时。
every time you successfully
connect to server.
下次会自动检查的
It's automatically gonna
check that next time.
但它们并非总是真实的。
But they're not always true.
>> Jem Young: 然后我们说用钥匙链，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
then we just say use keychain,
只说 SSH 密钥将会使用该密钥。
just saying the SSH key
is going to use that.
它会先看看锁链
It's gonna look in the keychain first,
而不是你必须手动通过它
rather than you have to
pass it through manually.
别担心其他的事情，因为这是我的工作电脑。
Don't worry about the other stuff,
that's because this is my work computer.
>> Jem Young: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: All right.
>> Jem Young: 然后，如果需要，可以使用 ssh-add -k 和
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And then if you need to,
you can use ssh-add -k and
如果你想把这个加到教学里
that will manually add that
to the teaching if you want,
如果您不想启用自动执行该操作。
if you don't want to enable
the doing it automatically.
但我认为大多数人的电脑都是给家里的人
But I would assume most people's computer
is set up is for people at home who
正在使用不同的配置，可能是完全不同的操作系统。
are using a different configuration, maybe
a different operating system entirely.
>> Jem Young: 只需将 SSH 放入我们的服务器中。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Just get
the SSH into our server.
我现在就在这等你
I'm gonna hold here for now.
但是 >> Jem Young: 我们已经开始了。
But
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And we're on.
我们现在正在服务器上。
We are on a server now.
我们在世界上的某个服务器上，具体取决于您的数据中心所在的位置。
We're on a server somewhere in the world
depending on where your data center is.
重要的是要注意这个哈希，奥托索普
Important things to note,
this hash, octothorpe,
不管你想说什么我们都是超级用户
whatever you want to call it,
that means we're on as a superuser.
我们是小组成员
We're on as the group.
现在，根是危险的，我们要做的第一件事就是
Now, being root is dangerous, and one of
the first things we're gonna do is we're
因为根，它会让你做任何你想做的事情。
gonna switch out of root, because root,
it will let you do anything you want.
你想删除你的整个目录你想把所有东西都移走
You wanna remove your entire directory,
you wanna move everything,
它会让你做的
it'll let you do it.
它不会给你任何警告
It won't give you any warnings.
当我们转换为超级用户时，这意味着如果我们做一些事情，
When we switch out of being a super user,
it means if we do something that is
限制在许可权中，我们必须每次手动覆盖。
restricted in permissions, we have to
manually override that every time.
我们不想再这样了
We don't want to go around that.
真的很容易以 root用户的方式做任何事情。
It's really really tempting to
be to do everything as root.
但是因为没有根护栏，而是假定你知道自己是什么
But because there are no guardrails as
root, it's assuming you know what you're
你可以把自己变成一个糟糕的地方
doing, you can get yourself
into a really bad spot.
但稍后我们将学习如何创建一个新用户，
But a little bit later we're going to
learn how to create a new user that
具有 root 许可权，但缺省情况下不是 root用户。
has root permissions, but
by default is not root.